I am Alice, Integrity Knight!
Alice Synthesis 30!
I am the Proxy of the Three
Goddesses, who protect this realm!
I am the Priestess of Light,
and whoever dares defy me shall
know the fury of my power!
Alice...
Alicia...
This time...
This time her soul will be mine.
And once I have the light cube that
holds her Flux Light in my hands,
I'm going to savor every last bite.
Subjects, your attention.
We are heading south.
Pugilists in the lead, then Dark
Knights, then the Supply Corps.
That Knight is the Priestess of Light
and she is to be captured unharmed.
I am the opposite direction
of the rightf blunt.
Girl, you can lessen the rightf blunt.
To expect this to be a obvious?
I'm not sure about the rightf blunt.
I think a way to be surprised.
Never said it could be.
This is a new life.
I will not be able to act.
I can always tell you.
I am unable to act.
I will never do more!
I will never forget.
This answer is?
I will be able to change your mind.
I will be able to change my mind.
I will be able to get
you by making
sure I am.
I will be able to change my mind.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
The plan's working a little too well.
Vector's got his whole
army coming after you now.
He's obsessed with you,
no doubt about that.
We should be thankful he is.
It is much better than
being ignored entirely.
Alright, let's talk about strategy.
I was thinking me and
the troops keep leading
them south and slowly
chip away at their ranks.
Seems like the best approach. Agreed.
We have already wiped out
half of their numbers.
That leaves their main force,
the Dark Knights and Pugilists.
Chasing us will wear them down.
And if we can defeat Emperor Vecta,
I have hope the remaining people of
this land will be open to a truce. Hmm.
That's a good hope to have.
Problem is, who's going to be in
charge here when Vecta's gone?
If only that punk Shasta
was still alive then it
is true the general of
the dark knights is dead.
Yeah I didn't see him or
his number two out there
he would have been our
best shot to reason with.
I finished my reconnaissance
sir the shrubland
south of here should work for our ambush.
Thanks for checking it out, kid.
Tell the units and get
them ready to move out.
That dragon of yours
must be exhausted by now.
Make sure it gets food and
water before we go. Sir!
What is it? Oh, nothing.
I was just thinking.
Part of me's glad there won't
be any more synthesis rituals.
I mean, having your
memory and life stolen,
that's a horrible price
to pay to be a knight.
But then,
part of me is also kind of
sad if we won't be seeing
any more young 'uns like
Renly joining the Order.
Perhaps we won't.
However, stolen memories and
lives do not make a knight.
I know of no such rule, Uncle. Do you?
When we are all gone, our
souls, our will, our purpose,
they remain to inspire
those we leave behind.
That is what I believe.
Here they come.
Damn pugilists.
They'll be a handful for us.
If you hit them with your bare
fists, they'll happily take it.
But if you come at them with a
sword, they refuse to get cut.
What? Refuse?
Yep, that's what I said.
See, the more training they go through,
the more they think a sword's
nothing to be scared of.
So watch out when you fight them,
because they can will their skin to get
hard, and they can deflect any blade.
We'll have to keep them busy, till the
others are in position for the ambush.
I shall go and face them.
I can't wait to fight one of them
super-strong Integrity Knights!
Who are you supposed to be?
And why are you in the way?
Hmm.
I am a knight.
I am here to keep you
from advancing further.
By the looks of you, you couldn't
stop a kid from getting by.
Wait, let me guess.
All you can do is cast arts, right?
Hmm.
I am not skilled in formal arts.
Whatever.
Go kick her ass, Yote.
You got it!
Just you then?
I'm way more than you
can handle, you beanpole!
Now shut up and draw your sword!
Damn, that's skinny.
I'll break you in half!
I've heard that you prefer
keeping to yourself.
Why is that, I wonder?
Do people scare you?
Or perhaps, your urge to
slice them scares you.
I knew it.
I can see in your eyes that it does.
If you had your way, you'd
slice up everything in sight.
You feel like you're cursed
with a drive for murder.
Cheer up.
There's no reason to
feel ashamed about it.
In fact, I can help you
use it to your advantage.
On your last reconnaissance
mission into the Dark Territory,
you brought this flower back to me.
It absorbed massive amounts of the spatial
resources generated on the battlefield.
I will turn it into your divine object,
a sword with the highest priority
level that can cut through anything.
With this sword, you shall wield a manifestation
of the curse carved into your soul.
Take it and serve me with
your murderous impulse.
The curse you were born
with now has a purpose.
Slice and hack and slash away.
And at the end of your blood-smeared path,
you will find the key
to breaking your curse.
At least, you might.
What a savage fighting
style and yet as violent
as her attacks are I do
not detect any hostility or
any emotion for that
matter I've known her for
more than a hundred years
and I still have no idea?
what goes on in her head.
Not even a clue.
Don't worry about her,
she can handle them.
But we should go before
the main force catches up.
Come on, we have to make sure
everyone's ready and waiting for them.
Right.
All the units are in position.
According to Commander Bercoli, the
pugilists are vulnerable to sacred arts.
The planes might not have
enough spatial resources,
but here, there's at
least some vegetation,
so the priests should have enough
sacred power to launch an attack.
Hopefully it'll cause confusion, and
we can use our dragons to burn them.
Are the supply corps somewhere safe?
Yes.
They're standing by to the south.
They're far enough back that they
won't get caught in the battle.
Very good. Thank you.
Come on, man.
I'm getting bored sitting
around giving orders.
How's about we go outside
and have ourselves some fun?
No thanks, but you can
go first if you want to.
I'll pick a spot.
There, in those woods.
That better be where the action
is or I'm gonna be disappointed.
I guarantee you'll have fun.
P-King, that is.
Five down, baby.
How dare you!
You're gonna pay for this! Yes!
These fists are mine.
Your armor's nothing but paper!
Well, well, well.
You might look like a girl,
but you're as hard as a rock.
I am not a girl.
I am older than you. Huh?
Yeah, I know you are.
You're an Integrity Knight.
You're all supposed to be
immortal freaks or whatever.
So what?
Do you want me to call you Granny instead?
I'll allow it.
However, you are also freakish.
Your skin is so hard, I
could barely cut into it.
Deal with it, Granny.
Besides,
folks like us need an edge against you
knights but with your demon powers and all.
You charged in and chopped up all my pe -
You maimed him.
You were holding back, weren't you?
What do you think we
are, training dummies?
You're taking pity on us?
I'm gonna beat you to death personally!
Here I come, woman!
What did you expect?
That all his putilists did was punch?
See ya!
Now that your armor's gone, you're
looking way more like a fighter.
Although, you don't got
nearly enough muscles.
You should eat and train more.
Woman, as should you,
just now you became a bit softer.
Are you calling soft?
I was just getting warmed up.
Now that I am, you're
gonna see me at full power.
So don't hold back.
Give me all you got.
Then wipe that.
Sleepy look off your face already!
I trust that will suffice. Come then.
Alright, you asked for it.
I'm so fired up for this.
I never fought anyone like her before.
Strange how I allow
this battle to continue.
It must be this one's attack.
He seems weak everywhere except his fists.
But he displays a will worthy
of an Integrity Knight.
I could end this by cutting off his head.
I should, but I wonder if I
can slice through that fist.
This is fun.
Even though she looks like
some weak upper class lady
from the human empire deep
down She's the same as me.
Oh she's gonna overpower me.
Oh well if I'm gonna die
this ain't a bad way to go.
What in the hell did
you do that for, Donpa?
We're out of time, champion.
Main force is almost here.
Hey, woman!
Don't you go thinking you won this fight!
Look here.
I do have a name.
Not woman. Whatever.
The main force is almost here
and we got you surrounded, so...
Lousy dragons.
Go on and go!
But at least tell me your
name before you run away!
I am not running away.
And for your information,
my name is ShetaSynthesis12.
That's it.
A little closer.
Sup, baby doll.
How'd you spot me?
It wasn't too hard.
My mentor taught me to trust
my senses, not my eyes. What?
Where have I heard that?
Wake up!
The enemy's here!
Oh, boys!
Time to party!
What?
The enemies behind us?
Dozens of them?
If they destroy our supplies,
we will be immobilized.
And those two girls and
Kirito are back there.
I should send backup.
But if I do, the enemy
will know about our ambush.
Or could they already know?
Maybe I should send all of
these troops back to help.
I guess they figured we'd head
this way after we broke through.
So they stuck some troops
down here to meet us.
Commander!
Hmm, Renly.
Get the troops up and out of here.
Kiddo, go and help the Supply Corps.
I'll stay here and hold off the pugilists.
Understood?
Sir!
You say you'll hold them off. But how?
They are 5,000.
You are but one.
Kid, don't worry. I got this.
Now get going.
All right, then.
Please be safe.
Ronier!
There it is.
That old feeling.
Goddamn, I missed the rush of it.
A life hanging by the edge of my sword.
This right here's why I can't
get enough of player killing.
Uh-huh... Huh?
Is that Lady Stacia?
The secret room's opening up!
Holy crap, you've got to be kidding me.
Same hair, same face, it's her.
The killer queen of the
Knights of the Blood Oath.
Lightning Flash
It's so sad that it's so sad
I can't live
alone I don't want
anyone to love you I don't know
why I'm so happy You're the scent
You're the talking
I'm still in the body I'm
still in love
I'm the dream